{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947256955110","data":{"timestamp":" 947256955110"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000107_175420"," gameId":" 2bc35000-8dba-4c92-941b-98e23b1609c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_626_626-479-143"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 626"," userResponse":" 143"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947256992036","data":{"timestamp":" 947256992036"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000107_175420"," gameId":" 2bc35000-8dba-4c92-941b-98e23b1609c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_626_626-479-143"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 626"," userResponse":" 479"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947257010814","data":{"timestamp":" 947257010814"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000107_175420"," gameId":" 2bc35000-8dba-4c92-941b-98e23b1609c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_626_626-479-143"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 626"," userResponse":" 626"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947257027411","data":{"timestamp":" 947257027411"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000107_175420"," gameId":" 2bc35000-8dba-4c92-941b-98e23b1609c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_461_261-461-429"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 461"," userResponse":" 461"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947257053587","data":{"timestamp":" 947257053586"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000107_175420"," gameId":" 2bc35000-8dba-4c92-941b-98e23b1609c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_545_440-545-211"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 545"," userResponse":" 545"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947257073644","data":{"timestamp":" 947257073644"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000107_175420"," gameId":" 2bc35000-8dba-4c92-941b-98e23b1609c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_786_786-588-175"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 786"," userResponse":" 786"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947257092015","data":{"timestamp":" 947257092015"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000107_175420"," gameId":" 2bc35000-8dba-4c92-941b-98e23b1609c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_761_761-242-414"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 761"," userResponse":" 761"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947257115176","data":{"timestamp":" 947257115176"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000107_175420"," gameId":" 2bc35000-8dba-4c92-941b-98e23b1609c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_324_324-285-326"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 324"," userResponse":" 285"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947257154824","data":{"timestamp":" 947257154824"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000107_175420"," gameId":" 2bc35000-8dba-4c92-941b-98e23b1609c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_324_324-285-326"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947257172300","data":{"timestamp":" 947257172300"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000107_175420"," gameId":" d8b59a45-85db-46ef-93a9-63285d36951c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947257174304","data":{"timestamp":" 947257174304"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000107_175420"," gameId":" d8b59a45-85db-46ef-93a9-63285d36951c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947257177290","data":{"timestamp":" 947257177290"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000107_175420"," gameId":" d8b59a45-85db-46ef-93a9-63285d36951c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947257179008","data":{"timestamp":" 947257179008"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000107_175420"," gameId":" d8b59a45-85db-46ef-93a9-63285d36951c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947257181505","data":{"timestamp":" 947257181505"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000107_175420"," gameId":" d8b59a45-85db-46ef-93a9-63285d36951c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIANGAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947257185132","data":{"timestamp":" 947257185131"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000107_175420"," gameId":" d8b59a45-85db-46ef-93a9-63285d36951c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947257185893","data":{"timestamp":" 947257185893"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000107_175420"," gameId":" d8b59a45-85db-46ef-93a9-63285d36951c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947257217385","data":{"timestamp":" 947257217385"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000107_175420"," gameId":" d8b59a45-85db-46ef-93a9-63285d36951c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947257225725","data":{"timestamp":" 947257225725"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000107_175420"," gameId":" d8b59a45-85db-46ef-93a9-63285d36951c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}